[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of movie is the 1988 British film The Fruit Machine, also known as Wonderland in the United States?", "correct_answer": "Thriller movie", "incorrect_answers": ["Animated movie", "A biographical account", "Comedy movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the doll that says Momma?", "correct_answer": "Alexander Graham Bell", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Ford", "Benjamin Banneker", "Thomas Alva Edison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks have poor vision.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why isnt the baby elephant able to control its trunk?", "correct_answer": "Because it lacks muscle tone", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Because it is too heavy for it", "Because it cannot feel it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People who are lactose-intolerant should not consume yogurt or milk.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these US states comes in North and South flavours?", "correct_answer": "Dakota", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia", "Washington", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state of Tennessee, USA has 2 Time Zones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is silent movie is also the oldest on the American Film Institute (AFI) list of the Top 100 American films, and its ranked # 44.", "correct_answer": "The Birth of a Nation", "incorrect_answers": ["Wings", "The Jazz Singer", "It Happened One Night"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Noahs Boy refers to a fish sandwich.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fear of stars and celestial space is known as astrophobia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the smallest bat species on the planet, endemic to the Asian continent?", "correct_answer": "Kittis Hog-nosed Bat", "incorrect_answers": ["Mouse-tailed Bat", "Sucker-footed Bat", "Bulldog Bat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The longest coma lasted approximately this long.", "correct_answer": "37 years", "incorrect_answers": ["2 years", "11 months", "24 years"]}]